asslikethat.com 2016-02-13

# AssLikeThat : Privacy Policy

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**The Information We Collect:** This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on website. On some pages, you can order products/subscriptions, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

Name:  
Email address:   
Address:   
City:   
State:   
Country:   
Zip:   
Username:  
Password: 

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use the username and password information to pass that info onto the specified processor to help speed up the transaction process. Your email address is stored securely, and only used if the subscriber agrees to receive promotional materials. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security:**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by emailing [getmyinfo@asslikethat.com](mailto:getmyinfo@asslikethat.com). We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How To Contact Us:**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [Support](mailto:support@asslikethat.com). 

© Copyright 2003-2004 ASSLIKETHAT.com., All Rights Reserved
